# **Anthony Segedi**

40 Hungerford Rd | London, N7 9LP | aj.segedi@gmail.com | +44 7598 279287 | LinkedIn | Portfolio

## Summary

I have been developing and testing software for ~3 years on a wide range of applications in Java and PHP, and utilized both MySQI & OracleSQL databases. I thoroughly enjoy and have excelled in my current role, but I am looking for new opportunities to stay with my partner in England. Please visit my portfolio if you are interested in more details regarding my technical skill experience or if you want to see some animated fireworks!

## Experience

Midwest Insurance | Application Developer

Oct 2022 - Current

- Implement new features and updates across a diverse set of applications and use cases
  - Java based insurance & financial application backed by OracleSQL database
  - PHP/GWT based website backed by MySQL database
- Manage multiple virtual machine backed Tomcat/Jboss servers with Vagrant (Vsphere)
- Thoroughly test peer developer patches creating and executing QA test plans with evidence report
- Monitor deployed patch functionality in a Jenkins continuous integration production environment
- Mandatory VeraCode security training on threats and risk aversion techniques including OWASP top 10 security vulnerabilities
- Completed project highlights:
  - Expanded document printing internal systems and document templates to send 18 new documents (previously only 1) and developed a REST client (with the Jersey client framework) for the new API
  - Integrated delinea secret server with internal application authorizations to enhance security using secret server's REST API and the Guzzle PHP client framework
  - Refactored multiple Spring Batch jobs for internal applications including a job that synchronizes user accounts using LDAP queries with Microsoft Azure Active Directory

Varsity Tutors | Independent Contractor: CS and Programming Tutor

June 2022 - Feb 2023

- Tutored university students in data structures, memory models (stack, heap, pointers), generics, streams, and more
- Covered multiple programming languages including Java, C, and Python
- Tailored content to help students understand complex topics, including recap lectures and demonstration programs featuring classroom algorithms and topics
- Achieved a 5 star rating and greatly improved student understanding and project scores
- Prioritized my students after starting a full time job, continuing tutoring through the end of their semesters to ensure they had the best possible outcomes

### Education

University of Wisconsin-Madison | Madison, WI

Sept 2019 - May 2022

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

Graduate Level Courses: Operating Systems (Incl. Concurrency), Graphics, Networking

#### Skills

Languages: Java, C, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, PHP, Python, PowerShell, Bash, MySQL, Oracle SQL, PL/SQL Skills: Data Analysis, Collaboration, Problem Decomposition, Abstraction